Hey guys something happened that you guys
buenos chavales ha pasado una cosa que
sent me a lot today ok I'm going to check it out and
me habéis mandado muchísimo hoy ok voy a
see how it is and it's that I
verlo a ver qué tal y es que me he
found out that he was going to go there and make fun of
enterado que iba ahí vuelve a tirar
Dallas again
pullas a dallas
honestly it was because of the forum eye eye this forum this forum this
honestamente era por el foro ojo ojo
new forum me chavalería dot com which I'm
este nuevo foro me chavalería punto com
counting on although you'll all be
el cual cuento aunque todos estaréis ya
registered already ok at the time of
registrados vale en el momento de hoy
uploading this today
subiendo esto
this forum is going to be the new source of
este foro va a ser la nueva fuente del
salsa where all the
salsero a la que todos los canales de
sal channels are going to go I'll leave it there I'll
sal se os van a acudir lo dejo ahí lo
leave it there you'll see if you want to be
dejo ahí ustedes veréis si queréis ser
the first to find out
los primeros enterados
I'm out there all day chatting and
yo estoy por ahí todo el día charlando y
chatting at least taking a look at
chatea por lo menos echando un vistazo a
the things that happen to me there okay and it turns out I
las cosas que me pasa ahí vale y resulta
came here today
que me vengo aquí hoy
and he goes there
y va ahí
and says ibai plays with dallas
y dice ibai juega con dallas al amor
I get into love
me meto
and there's a video
y hay un vídeo
but in this case the conflict between
pero en este caso el conflicto entre
dallas review and iba and we don't know what it's
dallas review e iba y ya no sabemos qué
going to be dedicated to many videos
va a estar dedicado muchos vídeos ahí va
this is going to be about what he said at the time he
a ir esto por lo que en su tiempo dijo
was going to be
iba a ir
about dallas review very
respecto a dallas review comentarios muy
very strong comments very  disgusting but now
muy fuertes muy asquerosos pero ahora
we come for a specific issue
venimos por un tema en específico el
which is about VAT and plains and how I wanted to
cual es sobre iva y llanos y como quería
make peace for doing it with Dallas
hacer las paces por hacérselo con dallas
review and this the passes I do
review y esto la pases
n't think I've already said this will be a
no creo que ya lo he dicho esto será un
clip I've
clip
already said it many times if I
ya ya lo he dicho muchas ocasiones si yo
had had the intention of stopping
hubiera tenido intención de frenar
the hate I would have done it by talking to
el hate hubiera hecho por hablar con
Dallas or sending a message like
dallas o mandar un mensaje en plan
when to upload the first video to have
cuando dar a subir el primer vídeo haber
made him in a string some statements
hecho el en un string unas declaraciones
because I put them like others have done not like hey
porque los pongo como han hecho otros no
look have you seen the
en plan oye mira ha visto el vídeo de
Dallas video and I'm sincerely sorry for
dallas y sinceramente lo siento por
all the things I said he has the past they
todas las cosas que dije tiene el pasado
no longer represent me I joined the mob
ya no me representan me sumé a la turba
and hey Dallas for my part I ask your forgiveness
y oye dallas por mi parte te pido perdón
and will never again make those
y ya nunca más volverá a ser esos
comments does he think he is innocent blah blah blah
comentarios se cree inocente bla bla bla
blah dedicate two minutes to him okay dedicate
bla dedicarle dos minutos vale dedicarle
two minutes what is happening from my
dos minutos qué es lo que pasa desde mi
point of view I think it is that he was going to
punto de vista yo creo que es que iba a
go he doesn't want to do that and he will never
ir no quiere hacer eso y nunca va a
do that because of the people that surround him
hacer eso por por la gente que los rodea
because of the people that surround him people
por la gente que le rodea la gente le
would tell him not to give him away Dallas you are
diría no le des volar dallas le estás
giving him and I think he is going  there I would have
dando y yo creo que sí va ahí hubiera
uploaded that video
subido ese vídeo no hubieran existido
the other 4 or 5 videos would not have existed the talk would have been
los otros 4 ó 5 vídeos que la charla no
pointless you saw your cameo in the
tendría sentido viste tu cameo en el
video of forming a red heart without the snis
vídeo de forman corazón rojo sin el snis
take a look but now we see it
le echa un vistazo pero ahora lo vemos
now we see it okay it's
ahora lo vemos vale
not that it was not convenient for him and I, for me, for me it was
no es que no le convenía y yo yo para mí
going to be from the first
yo para mí sí iba desde el primer
moment, from the first video I would have
momento desde el primer vídeo hubiera
done that it's that he could have stopped it
hecho eso es que lo pudo haber frenado
before the first video remember and you
antes del primer vídeo acordaros y esto
can check this because I have
lo podéis comprobar porque yo tengo aquí
a video here on the secondary channel reading
un vídeo en el canal secundario leyendo
sostres dallas
sostres dallas
warning on twitter long before it was going to
aviso en twitter mucho antes de que iba
be a video I was going to put the
a ser un vídeo iba a ir poniendo la
capture of the tweets and bye there
captura de los tweets y bye
was nothing there I was already going there I could have
ahí no había nada ahí ya iba ahí podía
cut it short what is
haberlo cortado por lo sano qué es lo
going on well that the environment was going to be there
que pasa pues que iba a estar el entorno
give them the capo gets along with him Felipe is
dales el capo se lleva con él felipe es
the best he gets along with all those people who would have been
el mejor se lleva con toda esa gente que
upset that he was
a los que le hubiera sentado mal que iba
there would have mediated these people do not want to
ahí hubiera mediado esta gente no quiere
mediate with Dallas these people want to
mediar con dallas esta gente quieren
treat Dallas as an outcast
tener a dallas como un apestado
there are many people who say no but of course
hay mucha gente que dice no pero claro
how are they going to apologize and vice  after
cómo se va a disculpar y vice después de
all the insults from dallas I
todos los insultos del dallas los
enjoy them they have come in the videos
disfruto han venido en los vídeos
later
después
and not that they are tremendous fruits
y tampoco que sea unos frutos tremendos
or rather what he says
o sea que le dice
is tremendous put it on a scale
es tremendo ponérmelo en una balanza por
please with me calling him fart with him laughing what
favor con que le llame pedo con que se
good is it to him on the channel make
ría de que le sirve en el canal haga
jokes that they are going to put him in jail
bromas de que lo van a meter preso
if someone tells me that any of the
si alguien me dice que alguno de los
supposed insults that he
insultos supuestos insultos que da la
said to ibai are worse than that
dicho a ibai son peores que eso
show it to me and let's see if I
que me lo muestre y de a ver si se lo
buy it no
compro no
but what such a way
pero qué tal manera
and goes there he could have stopped him he
y va ahí lo pudo haber frenado lo
would have stopped him at the moment he should have
hubiera frenado en el momento debió
software hey if it's
software oye si es verdad yo
true I hey if it's true I'm sorry I put this to you right now I delete the tweets and I tell you from here that I'm sorry but no because then they go to their friends the neighbor attacks that's it but dallas has been like dallas has been on youtube well on the
el dallas ha sido en youtube bueno en
internet
internet
the kid who is bullied okay
el chaval al que le hacen bullying vale
be the whole [ __ ] internet
sea todo el [__] internet haciéndole
bullying him like he was the plague and
bullying como si fuera la peste y
winning it all I in my day was part of
ganándolo de todo yo en su día parte de
it
ello
many of us have been part of it but me
muchos hemos sido parte de ello pero yo
rectify once you realize and that's it
rectifica una vez que te das cuenta y ya
the problem ends, I
se acaba el problema
say I say
digo yo digo yo
a little bit in context sir and let's go
un poquito en contexto señor y vayamos
together with his friends they were playing
junto con sus amigos estaban jugando a
him at among aus and in one of those
él al among aus y en una de esas se
a subscriber of theirs was placed or
colocó algún suscriptor de ellos o sea
rather out of nowhere because they were missing one and
así de la nada porque les faltaba uno y
well, the subscriber snuck in but the
pues vaya el suscriptor se coló pero lo
interesting thing about this is that the subscriber was
interesante de esto es que el suscriptor
called de las changing the name and
se llamaba de las cambiando el nombre y
the word to by law so that
la palabra a por la ley para que así
each subscriber I have a friend
cada suscriptor yo tengo un amigo que se
called de los on twitter a twitter or
llama de los en twitter un twitter o
well he managed with person came to my house it would
bueno logró con persona venía a mi casa
n't look so obvious and this was the
no se viera tan obvio y esta fue la
reaction of iba there for each part they
reacción de iba ahí por cada parte les
had to be the killers together
tocó juntos justamente ser los killers
and if we vote vote by vote
y si votamos de voto a voto
for example they literally play the
por ejemplo me tocan literalmente la
basic game
partida básica
what or why do you appear this
qué o para qué aparece usted esta
reaction I
reacción
don't want to say anything I don't know
no quiero decir yo nada decir no sé de
what you think of this reaction from ibai
qué os parece esta reacción de ibai
when he reads that his partner in the game
cuando lee que su compañero en el juego
is called the last it
se llama the last
couldn't have for example I have a
no podría haber por ejemplo yo tengo un
friend on twitter called de los and he
amigo en twitter que se llama de los y
doesn't do it as a reference to dallas he
no lo hace como referencia a dallas
could have taken it and passed  if he doesn't
podría haber cogido y haber pasado si no
want to make references to Dallas
nos quiere hacer referencias a dallas
if he goes and doesn't want to make reference to
si va y no quiere hacer referencia a
Dallas he
dallas
would have taken he would have
hubiera cogido
taken and that the last what's his
hubiera cogido y that the last cómo se
name
llama
from the
de la esfera
wool sphere of the night seeds
de lana de las pepas de la noche
and if he had acted crazy as if
y si hubiera hecho el loco como si no
the name doesn't sound familiar
les sonará el nombre
but this is how epic this forced laughter
pero esto qué épico esta risa forzada
with him
con él
and then maybe I was there I started to make
y después igual iba ahí empecé a hacer
a series of comments about the
una serie de comentarios sobre el
character in question that being here
personaje en cuestión que estar aquí
good night the words stop because
buenas noches las palabras para porque
I was working with him like that I'm not
yo estuve trabajando con él así no lo
going to do anything
voy a hacer nada
I feel like it there's the partition of 9 and
me apetece que está la partición de 9 y
a big well it seems incredible to me he has
un big well me parece increíble se ha
joined what the other one said
unido que ha dicho el otro
stop stop stop let's see again then
para para para a ver de nuevo después
maybe I was there I started to make a series
igual iba ahí empecé a hacer una serie
of comments about the character in
de comentarios sobre el personaje en
question that being here
cuestión que estar aquí
good night like two of the words stop
buenas noches así dos de las palabras
because I was working with him
para porque yo estuve trabajando con él
like that I'm not going to do anything it's that he
así no lo voy a hacer nada es que ha
said I was working with fabrics and I'm not
dicho estuve trabajando con telas y no
going to do anything weird he refers to something
lo voy a hacer nada raro se refiere algo
from the game maybe let's
del juego quizás
see if really dude he really
a ver si de verdad tío de verdad
gives me more cricket and the fanatics than Ibai
me da más cricket y los fanáticos que el
himself dude I
propio ibai tío
really have nothing against
de verdad no tengo nada en contra de
this man to me no man  nabai as if
este hombre a mí no macho nabai como si
as if tomorrow I have to Uruguay or go to
como si mañana tengo que uruguay oa la
hell with him, he hasn't done anything to me, I
mont con él a mí no me ha hecho nada yo
'm just objectively commenting on
solamente estoy comentando objetivamente
what's going on, but the fanatics and I have to,
lo que hay pero los fanáticos y yo me
the support is there already in the chat
toca es la apoya está ahí ya en el chat
saying, of course he's laughing, he's going to
diciendo pues claro que se ríe que va a
make
hacer llorar
me cry, man, well, he's simply laughing
tío pues simplemente se está riendo
because he's making a reference to
porque está haciendo una referencia a
Dallas, I
dallas
could simply take it and ignore it
podría [__] y de las ignorarlo
completely
totalmente
and search, search where it's not clear
y buscar es buscar donde no hay claro
exactly, it
exactamente
pains me that the whole part of 9
me apena que toda la parte de 9 me
seems incredible to me
parece increíble
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
spectacular
espectacular
of the spectacular of the
de las espectaculares de las
spectacular of the representing hits
espectacular de la representando azota a
a spectacular but in the end she went, she
una espectacular pero al final iba ella
told us the following, apart they won or
nos dijo lo siguiente aparte ganaron o
apart they both stayed together of the of the of
se aparte quedaron los dos juntos de las
the 20 of the sales of the 20
de las de las 20 de las ventas de las 20
of the come to the left of the come to
de las ven a la izquierda de las ven a
the left of the left of the of the of the of the of
la izquierda de la izquierda las de las
the matas
de las de las de las matas
there he made a mistake and said
ahí se ha equivocado y ha dicho
Dallas
dallas
if he's wrong or not let's see
si se equivoca o no a ver
the week of the matas let's see let's
las de la semana de las matas a ver
see the transcript,
vamos a ver la transcripción
the transmission understood the [ __ ]
la transmisión la entendió la [__]
[ __ ] of thirst of  more of the bushes I'm
[__] de sed de más de las matas yo
here nothing besides towel and the bushes
aquí nada además toalla y las matas
to see every shitty transcription let's
a ver cada [__] de transcripción vamos
fight it again because I think if
a lucharlo de nuevo porque creo que si
the elas wrong
las elas equivocado
apart from winning or not apart from that
aparte ganar o no se aparte que hablaron
they both spoke together of the of the of the 20
los dos juntos de las de las de las 20
of the sales of the 20 of the you see on the
de las ventas de las 20 de las ven a la
left of the you see on the left I open
izquierda de las ven a la izquierda abro
of the good left of the of the of the of the of
de las buena izquierda las de las de las
the candles and the candles
de las de las velas y las velas
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
and whoever says that we don't get along I will
y quien dice que nos llevamos mal yo lo
see it I see that he is making a
veré yo veo que está haciendo una una
clear reference you know I see it very
clara referencia sabe yo lo veo
clearly I see a clear reference
clarísimo yo veo una clara referencia
arda the
arda la
when he is doing this of who says
cuando está haciendo esto de quien dice
that we don't get along it
que nos llevamos mal
seemed good to me
me pareció bien
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
the best agent spectacular of the
el mejor agente espectacular de la
spectacular represent basement
espectacular representan sótano
clearly represents this was referring to
claramente esto estaba refiriéndose a
the reviews this is the first time that I do
las reviews esta es la primera vez que
n't want to see it that I don't see it to whoever
no lo quiera ver que no lo veas a quien
is justifying it is not that he is not
esté justificando no es que no la está
making reference to anything
haciendo referencia a nada
write and as such speaks of Dallas
escriba y como tal habla de dallas
even that it was different from the of the of the
inclusive que estaba distinto de las de
being one of those
las de las siendo una de esas empresa de
city companies the ones of the fellings and then what I
ciudad las de las talas y después lo que
think is not they  I don't think he
creo que no ellos yo creo que no ha
said anything, I think he said what
dicho nada yo creo que ha dicho de la lo
happens is that when you say it quickly and you
que pasa que al pronunciarlo rápido y tú
know how to speak, I don't think he's
sabes la forma de hablar yo creo que no
wrong
se equivoca
about not liking each other and all that,
en que se caen mal y todo eso
obviously he was referring to the
evidentemente se estaba refiriendo a la
review, no, but well, maybe the gentleman was
review no pero bueno será que el señor
going and he has to make
iba y ya nos tiene que llevar las cosas
peace with Dallas, this is what he
en paz con dallas esto es lo que quiere
means with this 2 eat, it doesn't seem to me like making
decir con este 2 comer a mí no me parece
peace with Dallas, let's see, he didn't
llevar a la cosa en paz a ver tampoco ha
say anything bad either, but it would have been a
dicho nada malo pero hubiera sido una
good opportunity to clear something up, come on, hey, look, I do
buena oportunidad para aclarar algo pase
n't know what, I don't know how much,
oye mira no sé qué no sé cuánto
but he doesn't want to, he doesn't want to because then
pero no quiere no quiere porque entonces
his friends, it has
sus amigos
n't happened many times you're in a
no ha pasado muchas veces estáis en un
group of friends and all your
grupo de amigos y ya todos vuestros
friends don't like a person from the
amigos les cae mal a una persona del
neighborhood and you don't talk to him and you don't
barrio y usted no le habla y no le
talk to him because your friends are going to feel bad, you
habláis porque les va a sentar mal a tus
really wouldn't mind
amigos a ti en realidad no te importaría
talking to that person but your friends think you're
hablarte con esa persona pero tus amigos
outcasts, that's how
lo tienen como apestados
these people act, that's how these
así actúan esta gente así esto en esta
people act, but nevertheless, ibai has
gente pero sin embargo ibai no tiene
no problem, no qualms about playing
ningún problema ningún reparo en jugar
with the crazy person, let's
con el demente
remember that the crazy person admitted to
recordemos que el demente reconoció
fooling around on chat, on a chat, I don't
estar tonteando por chat por un chat no
remember  if they actually sent nudes or
me acuerdo si llegaron a mandarse nude o
not I don't remember I think I remember that he
no no recuerdo creo creo recordar que él
admitted that he asked for them in fact
admitió que se las pidió de hecho
they uploaded some screenshots okay be with the
subieron unas capturas vale sean con el
madman they have no problem playing and
demente no tienen un problema en jugar y
giving him fame okay that's how they
darle fama vale
are double double standards false
así son doble doble rasero falsedad
comments really well he could
comentarios realmente bien podría
apologize to Dallas either
disculparse con dallas ya sea por
privately or publicly about the things he
privado o por público sobre las cosas
said at the time about him and then
que dijo en su momento de él y ahí las
things would be as calm as if
cosas estarían tan tranquilas como si
nothing but well he was going there he hasn't had some
nada pero bueno iba ahí no ha hecho unas
public or private drinks towards the
copas públicas o privadas hacia de la
network and as you know if he goes there he knows what
red y como sabes si va ahí sabe lo que
the madman did he speaks from
hizo el demente habla desde la
ignorance please
ignorancia por favor
ariel could I give a tangerine to summer
ariel le pude dar una mandarina a summer
and
y
someone can give a tangerine to
alguien le puede dar una mandarina a
samari and her mental gyms and those
samari y sus gimnasios mentales y las
looking for a way to justify it all
buscando la forma de justificarlo todo
please give him a tangerine to
por favor darle una mandarina para que
eat okay because he's been having a bad time the whole
coma vale porque lleva todo el directo
time we're
lleva todo el rato que estamos en
live he's been having a bad time don't silence
directo pasándolo mal no silencia
gustavo don't silence nobody is having a bad time anymore it's that they are having a
gustavo no silencia ya nadie lo pasa mal
bad time with these things
es que lo pasan mal con estas cosas
so I don't know how all this is going to happen
así que no sé cómo vaya a suceder todo
it's the only thing we have and first
esto es lo único que tenemos y primero
is that as such the review was mentioned there
es que igual como tal iba ahí mencionada
in a live after a long
la review en un directo después de mucho
time no well let's see for me at least
tiempo no bueno a ver para mí al menos
for me very clearly it is but very
para mí clarísimamente sea pero
clearly it is not the first time that it is
clarísimamente no es la primera vez que
referred to dada this time perhaps it has
se refiere a dada esta vez quizás ha
been more of a face but for me in the
sido más de cara pero para mí en la
other occasions that we have already spoken on
otras ocasiones que ya hemos hablado en
this channel there has been a response towards
este canal ha habido respuesta hacia
dallas also
dallas también
for me yes I have a lot of hair the
para mí si yo tengo muchos pelos los
balls to me that is nothing by chance
[__] a mí eso de nada es casual
okay no
vale no
but what do you think of this how
pero ustedes qué piensan de esto qué
cute you are a head a father face
lindo eres una cabeza un padre cara
in love black heart be it a lot
enamorada corazón negro ya sea mucho
for me a pleasure to see you here man
para mí un placer verte por aquí hombre
a pleasure to see you here
un placer verte por aquí
here we are talking about salsa salsa
aquí estamos hablando de salsa de salsa
and toque we monetize top up and eye eye eye
y toque monetizamos top up y ojo ojo ojo
that here we are in put by ham
que aquí nos estamos en ponga por ham
that I found out that now you are the
que me enterado que ahora eres la
trend of by ham
tendencia de por ham
okay my weapon
vale mi arma
to know your opinion from here this of
para saber su opinión desde aquí este de
this important of all
este importante de todos
well my first day he told you or rather my
pues mi primer día le ha dicho o sea mi
opinion is that here there is a
opinión es que aquí hay un grupito
closed group of d
cerrado de d
of peña here there is a closed group of
de peña aquí hay un grupito cerrado de
peña that are like that like
peña que son así que eso así
literally that they have a closed group
literalmente que tienen un grupo cerrado
and that they only want to hang out with the
y que sólo se quieren llevar con los
cool ones with the wire mosto papi when
guays con los wire mosto papi cuando
when  You're going to come
cuando vas a venir
when you're going to come here so I can make you
cuando vas a venir aquí a que yo te haga
a habit or are you one of the cool ones
un hábito o eres de los guays
our daddy what side are you on of the
nuestro papi de qué bando eres de los
cool ones
guays
others or the outcasts like us
otros o de los apestados como nosotros
so the help didn't show daddy you
así que la ayuda no mostró papi tú
have a tail like the black guy from whatsapp
tienes el rabo como el negro de whatsapp
no ​​you have a tail like a black guy it's the
no tú tienes el rabo como un negro de
same you're taking it out here,
igual se tuco lo vas sacando por allí
there and here no
para allá y para acá no